The following tale begins on
June 5th in the year 1972.
It was a dark and humid night in
America's deep south when the first
cry of a newborn child rang through
the halls of a maternity hospital.
However,
before that baby had the
chance to see the light of day,
his life expired while still
curled in the arms of his mother.
To the young mother,
who had never once felt that
she had been living a life
that consisted of any
happiness or sense of purpose,
her newborn son
was going to be a symbol of the hope
that she would have a better future.
With her first child lost to her,
that potential happiness she
longed for was lost as well,
and she was unable to accept
his death.
Before the doctors and nurses could
learn of the baby's unfortunate passing,
the young mother slipped out of her bed
as if she were a phantom in the night.
She made her way into
another room where she
replaced her deceased
child with one who was
born the same day and made him her own.
This other baby which
she took was one of a set
of fraternal twins.
To this day, the incident was
never questioned or investigated,
and not Even a single
soul suspected a thing.
Mama, whose grave is this?
They were born the same day as me.
Died then, too.
Enrico. Huh?
The truth of the matter is,
you had a younger brother.
The two of you were fraternal twins. Huh?
But he passed away at the
hospital right after he was born.
Pray for him.
Afterwards, we decided to
give him the name Dominic.
Lord, answer my plea.
My brother and I were born on the
same day, but I lived and he died.
For what reason did fate choose to
take my brother's life and not mine?
And why do humans experience
happiness and misfortune?
What is true happiness?
At this time, Enrico was age 15.
His great-grandmother on his father's
side was an Italian immigrant.
He is descended from a prestigious
and influential family in Venice,
in which one of his family members became
a famous clergyman during
the 18th century. So,
when young Enrico declared he
wanted to attend a seminary,
there wasn't one member of
his family who objected.
Hey, is someone here? Who's there?
Tell me, what are you doing in here?
Hold it!
Is this book yours?
It's a famous biography
about a clergyman who
commits adultery and runs
off to become a painter.
Would a believer in God ever
read such a scandalous scripture?
Sergius, who are you?
How did you get in this place?
Except for on Sundays,
this charnel house does not allow
members of the general public to enter.
I am aware of the restrictions, but
I am deathly allergic to the sun.
If I am not mistaken, the
sun sets at 6.19 today.
Until that time comes, I cannot go
home, which is why I rested in here.
I see.
Well, in that case, is there
anything I can do to help you?
Not at all.
Okay.
That's unfortunate.
it.
I won't tell the head priest
about encountering you,
but you must be gone when the sun sets.
My, my.
You're an interesting one.
How so?
You're not going to throw me out.
What if I were a burglar who came
here to rob this place of its
most valuable artwork,
or worse, to kill you?
Or perhaps you're just saying I can stay,
but you actually plan to
rat me out to the police.
Is that what you want me to do?
Though a thief wouldn't lie about a
sun allergy, it doesn't seem plausible.
Not even the devil would
tell such a blatant lie.
Hold on a moment.
Did you just twist your ankle
because of me? Are you all right?
No, it isn't that.
Please don't worry about it.
I've been like this since my birth.
They say I was born with
twisted toes on my left foot.
However, it doesn't
hinder my ability to walk.
Do you believe in gravity
between individuals?
You ended up tripping
over me, of all people.
But did you know it was for a reason?
What are you saying?
Take this arrow.
Consider it a thank you present.
If you do not wish to accept it,
that is still perfectly fine with me.
But are not all meetings of
fate their own form of gravity?
We only did just meet, so I don't know
what your first impression of me is.
But I am a traveler fueled by
the hope of fateful encounters.
If ever you feel like
seeing me again someday,
aim that desire towards
the arrow and pray.
No matter how many years
might have passed since now.
Got it?
All I ask is for you to keep that in mind.
Once we reach sundown, it
shall be like I was never here.
What's this?
My toes!
The toes on my left foot!
They're not twisted!
Hey, wait!
Who even are you?!
Please father
Listen to my plea
I beg of you I have a confession to make
Yes well One moment I'll get the
priest I'm stricken with disease
And I fear I'm going to die
There's no cure That can help me now
But My illness isn't what
I'm here To confess about
My sin Was to my family
Sixteen years ago, on
the night of June 5th,
after my newborn baby drew his first and
final breath, I traded him for another.
While no one was looking, I took a
stranger's baby and left mine in his place.
That baby was a twin.
When I think about the baby's
parents, I am overcome with guilt.
Though he wasn't mine, I raised the
child to the best of my ability.
I was so happy,
and the little boy I watched go through
life grew up to be such a fine young man.
However,
if I die without ever confessing, what
would happen if I told him the truth,
that he has a brother somewhere?
Though if he finally learns what happened,
that would mean I've
lost my son before I die.
Are you familiar at all with who
the family of the other son is?
The other twins' family live in a
big mansion in the next town over.
Poochie is the family's last name.
I, like, really don't get it.
What exactly do you see in that
juice delivery boy, anyway?
I know.
But that butt, though.
Just stop it already.
I bet the loser comes from a poor family.
He probably doesn't
even go to high school.
That's why he delivers juice.
Hey, Perla!
Doesn't that bag belong to you?
No!
That guy just took it!
He's a purse snatcher!
Someone catch that guy!
God damn it.
I ended up breaking
out the store's window.
Totally gonna get fired from this job.
Plus, I'm not even allowed
to work under school policy.
Weather Forecast's real
name is Wes Aquamarine.
He was 16 at the time,
as innocent as anyone can be, and he had
a strong belief in the idea of justice.
So, uh, thanks a bunch.
You saved my purse back there.
Don't worry, I'll tell them he's
the one who broke the window.
Real?
Yes, of course.
Now you should go.
Um, my name's Wes.
Some people call me Weather.
You wanna hang?
Two months had passed since the dying
mother's life-changing confession,
and Enrico was in utter mental turmoil.
Although he hadn't become a priest yet,
Enrico was still bound
by the seal of confession
and could not disclose anything to anyone.
He had to keep it a secret at all costs.
Otherwise, in the eyes of the church,
he would be a failure as a man of God.
That mother will die soon, and she's going
to take her secret with her to the grave.
Even if I could convince
her to confess to everyone,
would we, or at the very
least, would my brother,
be able to continue living as a real
family even after knowing the truth?
I'm back.
Welcome home.
What's wrong?
Looks like you're spacing out.
Did something happen to you at school?
Promise me, big bro.
I'm begging you not to tell Mama and Papa!
My grades have sort of tanked recently.
I'll catch up eventually,
but what'll I do?
I have a boyfriend.
He's amazing.
I met him two weeks ago.
I really like him.
It's like our hearts are connected.
He's my soulmate.
Good for you, Perla.
Thanks, big bro.
Let's start with the conclusion.
The soon-to-be priest Enrico
never once uttered a word to his
sister about her new boyfriend Weather
being his younger twin brother.
From here on out in the story,
I would like you, the viewer,
to be the judge in deciding who is
the one who has committed a sin.
Was it the mother who had sinned
for having switched the babies?
The parents? Enrico?
Or was it Weather who didn't know a thing?
He looked into who
Weather was to learn who
it is that his sister
had fallen in love with.
After discovering the shocking truth In
Enrico's mind, there was only one solution.
No matter what the sacrifice, I have to
stop Perla from getting hurt in any way!
You look familiar, boy.
Ain't you the rich kid
who goes to a seminary?
Are you sure you want to be doing this?
If everything goes well,
I will double your pay.
There are only two
things I want you to do.
First, do not ask any questions.
And second, make these two break up.
I bet if I make a couple of thugs threaten
Wes, he'll break things off with Perla.
That is all.
The only thing Perla
will suffer from is an
ordinary heartbreak that
anyone would experience.
The scars that will be left
on her heart won't be fatal.
However,
what Enrico failed to
realize was the true nature
of this private detective
who he sought to hire.
This man who has a proclivity
for prying into secrets.
A man who holds a prejudice
deep within his heart.
One which stemmed from the inhumane laws
that dominated the South
just a century ago.
A prejudice that is very much still alive.
Goddamn sumbitch.
After doing some research on that West
kid, I discovered that back in 1972,
his whore mother married a black man,
all the while living in this very city.
So even though he looks white,
that boy is a black man's son.
After this revelation, the P .I.
rallied his clan together.
Don't worry that pretty
little head, sweetheart.
We're gonna be punishing him, not you.
That's right, baby.
Come here and give me
a kiss, why don't you?
Plant one on this nice
upstanding sheriff now, you hear?
You think you're all proper,
don't you little slut?
Lucky for you, you're a white girl, so
it don't matter who you fool around with.
But not that shit, Stone!
An animal like him can't be allowed to taste
those sweet lips of yours for a second!
Your older brother's the
one who asked me to do this.
And just so your ass is well aware, we've
already paid a visit to your mama's house!
So you know, your childhood
home is already up in flames!
In the end, who was the one truly
being punished in all of this?
Was it Weather? Perla?
Perhaps all anyone did up until this point
was love someone with all their heart.
The only truth that can be found is that
love brought about the worst-case scenario.
As for weather,
he was hung from a tree overlooking the
cliffside, and was left there to rot.
Until this day, Perla was pure of heart,
but the gentle breeze that once blew
through her heart swiftly came to an end.
Her love was like a spring sunshine.
However...
My heart will no longer
feel a thing anymore.
Not even while standing
in the rain. Nothing.
After uttering those words, Perla threw
herself off the cliff into the lake below,
taking her own life,
not knowing that her dearly beloved
weather still had a faint pulse.
Why in God's name? Why?
Why did it have to end like this?
Why did I even want to become
a priest in the first place?
Why does fate bring two people together?
If they hadn't met, none of
this would have ever happened.
Stop right there!
I'm telling you to stop that right now!
Don't you dare cross your
heart in front of my sister!
While I'm here, damn it all!
Please don't let this be the end!
Don't take your life away!
None of this was perilous! Fault!
All she did was fall in love!
I will do anything that you ask of me!
Just please bring her back!
If anyone should be damned
for this, then it's me!
Do you believe in gravity
between individuals?
Do you believe that fate brought
us together for a reason?
If you wish to see me again,
come and find me!
That was him!
It was the voice of that strange man!
I want to see him!
I've forgotten when!
But he's the man who healed my
foot back in the charnel house!
How could I have forgotten about?
Adam, until now, I just know
that he gave me something.
An arrowhead, if I recall.
What? What?
What is this?
The arrow that I've been
keeping in my pocket?
Once a life has been taken away,
it can never fully be given back.
But if your desire is strong enough,
and it's what you truly wish for,
You will be capable of
preserving her memory forever.
The memory that lives in her heart.
This, my new friend, is your awakening.
Hey, who the hell is there?
You're not that dumbass who asked me to
check if your wife's been cheating, are ya?
If you don't want to get pumped with lead,
I suggest you show that
ugly Mega you are...
YAH!
What the fuck?
Hey, you're big on information, yeah?
If you know so much, then tell me.
Why the hell is an infestation
of snails coming out of your arm?
Where do all these
snails keep coming from?
Why is it only happening around me?
Okay, who the fuck are you, God?
Is it true that Perla's brother
is the one who hired you?
Don't lie to me.
No, that can't be! How are you?
What's up with all these snails?
Why does this keep happening?
Damn it.
I really can't die.
Only when I try to use the gun,
the chamber's filled with water.
Why is it that I'm still alive?
Weather was filled with an immense rage.
He was mad at the world for having
to deal with everything around him.
Angry that he was still alive.
And furious at himself for feeling
responsible for Perla's death.
After realizing what happened to her.
Weather jumped off the cliff,
trying to follow her lead.
But a sudden gust of
wind blew him back up.
Then he tried to drown
himself in the lake.
But the strong waves would only
push him back onto the shore.
Why?
Why can't I just die and be with Perla?
In his despair, his rage
became a devastating fury.
His hatred started to extend
not only to the townspeople,
but to humanity in general.
On the fourth night, a major snail
infestation had invaded the town.
But why was it snails?
And where exactly did they come from?
No one was able to explain
this sudden occurrence.
The only person who understood
what was going on was Enrico,
who woke up in a hospital.
It's Wes.
No, it's Weather.
My brother isn't dead.
Since he and I share the same blood,
the awakening of my powers
must have awakened his own.
Just like how I wished for
the preservation of memories,
this must be what Weather
desired unconsciously.
If these snails were to start crawling
up my arm in order to do away with me,
I would have to finish off my brother.
I'm willing to do anything from now
on, even if that means I have to kill.
After I'm through with taking care
of weather, I shall go see that man.
The one who was named Dio.
Why does fate bring two people together?
I am convinced that he knows the answer.
That's what I want to learn.
The answer to that question is indeed the
strongest power this world may ever know.
And the ultimate truth.
Are you happy?
Your sister Perla ended up dying
because of your fucking request.
And now, my fury isn't satisfied.
I'll make you pay right here and now.
You're wrong.
I put this into motion
because I am your brother.
But that connection ends here today.
Weather, I'm going to eliminate you!
Oh, Weather, you are
merely a hindrance to me.
So I shall banish you
along with the Rainbow.
Like Perla, every one of
your memories will vanish.
And those without any memories
left are as good as dead.
You shall live out the rest of
your days like a caged animal.
Prisoner number MA152403
has been locked up!
My only reason for
continuing to live is to
settle the score with
him once and for all.
Are you saying they've come back to you?
You can remember everything now?
Then what are we doing here?
Shouldn't we be heading to
where Jolene is right now?
I only came with you for Jolene!
I don't give a damn about your past!
You don't want to go
where Jolene is currently.
It would just be useless.
And anyway, I need you by
my side so you can kill me.
You have to take my life.
Anastasia, I beg you.
And it's because of
this gruesome method of
eating that these bugs are
known as snail suckers!
Aurora!
Everyone, get in!
The suckers are crawling
in through the cracks!
What should we do, Jolene?
It doesn't matter if they're
in or out of the car.
Either way it goes, they're
gonna find us and start eating.
So while they're snacking,
we're going after weather!
Although you think I cope,
my head is filled with hope.
Of some place
other than here.
Although you think I smile.
Inside and all the while.
I'm wondering.
About my destiny.
I'm thinking about.
All the things I'd
like to do in my life.
I'm a dreamer.
A distant dreamer.
Dreaming far away.
From today.
Thank you.